<resources>
    <string name="appName">San PabLOOK</string>

    <!--NAVIGATION-->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="dine">Dine</string>
    <string name="book">Book</string>
    <string name="products">Products</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    <!--DASHBOARD TOURIST-->
    <string name="userName">Phil Nguyen</string>
    <string name="aboutUser">Hi I’m Phil, I’m an aspiring professional photographer!</string>
    <string name="follow">Follow</string>
    <string name="contactInfo">Contact Info</string>
    <string name="viewAll">View all >>></string>

    <!--NOTIFICATIONS-->
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="date">Aug 27 at 8:00 PM</string>
    <string name="notificationTitle">Trisha upvoted your review.</string>

    <!--CONTENT DESCRIPTIONS-->
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="profilePicture">Profile picture</string>
    <string name="editProfilePic">Edit Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="backButton">Back</string>

    <!--ACTIVITY HISTORY-->
    <string name="activityHistory">Activity History</string>
    <string name="destinationName1">Sampaloc Lake</string>
    <string name="destinationName2">St. Ambrose Chapel</string>
    <string name="destinationName3">Paraiso de Avedad</string>
    <string name="review1">\t\tVisited Sampaloc Lake in San Pablo City, Laguna, and it was an absolute gem! The serene beauty of this natural wonder left me spellbound. The picturesque surroundings and the tranquil waters make it a perfect escape from the hustle and bustle of city life. I had the chance to take a relaxing boat ride, which allowed me to fully immerse myself in the breathtaking scenery. The local culture and hospitality were heartwarming, and I enjoyed sampling some delicious local cuisine nearby.</string>
    <string name="review2">\t\tFirst time in Casa de San Pablo and YOU have to go! It’s the cutest little spot with amazing food. This place is to die for. IT WAS FIRE!! The service we received was so amazing and we will definitely be back again. They made us feel welcomed and gave us an amazing experience.</string>
    <string name="review3">\t\tThis place is great! Atmosphere is chill and cool but the staff is also really friendly. They know what they’re doing and what they’re talking about, and you can tell making the customers happy is their main priority. Food is pretty good, some classics and some twists, and for their prices it’s 100% worth it.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>